

MILAN KOVAČ

Software Developer

About Me

Ambitious, motivated, and always eager for new challenges and opportunities to gain valuable experiences. I assure you that I am committed to continuous growth as an engineer and as an individual. I am open to collaboration and look forward to opportunities that will enable me to achieve excellence.



+381612839646



milankovac75@gmail.com



kovac-milan

LANGUAGE

- English
- Serbian

SKILLS

- Node.js
- Nest.js
- Flutter
- •//PHP

EXPERIENCE

Forwardslash - Software Engineer Internship

Novi Sad - Feb 2021 - Mar 2021

- Working with the WordPress platform (theme creation, custom plugins, content management)
- Learning and improving skills in WordPress, PHP, Vue.js, Nuxt.js, and other relevant technologies

Forwardslash - Software Engineer

Novi Sad - Apr 2021 - May 2023

- Developing a WordPress Headless Application in combination with Vue.js / Nuxt.js
- Backend application development in Node.js / Nest.js
- Working with MySql and Postgres databases
- Developing Flutter mobile apps, using BLoC and Provider sate management
- AWS implementation of cognito service for authentication and authorization

Neotech Solutions - Software Engineer

Belgrade - Jun 2023 - Present

- Backend application development in Node.js / Nest.js
- Working with MongoDB database
- Working with AWS services

EDUCATION

Higher Education Technical School of Professional Studies in Novi Sad - VTSNS

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Information Technology 2018-2021

Higher Education Technical School of Professional Studies in Novi Sad - VTSNS

Master of Engineering - MEng, Information Technology 2021-2023